Hi Flora,
Thanks for your email. To answer your question,
my new school is great!
It’s very beautiful.
There are many modern buildings.
There’s a large sports field next to the teachers’ building.
All the students go there and do exercises together in the morning.
It’s amazing! Every Monday we raise the flag there.
It’s a special way to start the week.
The classroom building is behind the sports field.
We spend most of the time in our classroom.
It’s big and clean. Every week, we change seats.
This week I sit next to my best friend, Han Lin.
The dining hall is across from the sports field.
It’s my favourite place
because there are many kinds of food.
I love the Chinese food there.
They make delicious jiaozi.
How about your school?
Yours,Peter